Naturally, now that we have our action creators,
我们已经创建 action creator
the next thing we need to do is build out our Reducer to handle those actions.
下一步是创建处理这些 action 的 Reducer
So let's go ahead and we will create a brand new folder called,
新建一个叫做 reducers 的文件夹
Reducers and inside of here,
在该文件夹中
we will have an index.js file.
新建一个文件 叫做 index.js
And then what we will do- the first thing is
然后我们将
let's go ahead and import both of these constants.
导入这两个常量
So we will import or receive entries,
导入 RECEIVE_ENTRIES
as well as, add entries.
以及 ADD_ENTRIES
Both of these are coming from actions.
二者都来自 /actions
And then now, we're just going to have a single entries reducer and it's going to
现在创建一个 entries reducer
take in a state which we will set the default state to
它将传入一个 state 我们将默认 state 设为空的对象
be just an empty object and an action.
然后传入一个 action
And then now, as always we will have a switch statement here,
和平常一样 在这里创建一个 switch 语句
switching on, action.type, and then we will have a few different cases.
对 action.type 进行切换 然后设定几个不同的 case
The first one is going to be the Receive Entries.
第一个是 RECEIVE_ENTRIES
The next one is going to be,
第二个是 ADD_ENTRY
Add Entry and the last one is just going to
最后一个是默认 case
be our Default case which will just return the States.
它将直接返回 state
And before I forget, let's go ahead and export this.
先导出这个 以防我忘记了
Alright, so now what we want to have happen is whenever the receive entries case matches,
每当符合 RECEIVE_ENTRIES case 时
whenever action.type is receive entries what we want to do
即每当 action.type 是 RECEIVE_ENTRIES 时
is we want State to be exactly the same
我们希望 state 保持不变
as it is but we also want to merge action.entries on it.
并且在 state 上合并 action.entries
Because if you remember,
action.entries
action.entries is this right here.
位于这里
And what this is going to be,
它将表示一个对象
is it's going to be an object with each key
该对象的键
representing a specific day and the value being the specific metrics for that day.
代表的是具体的某一天 值是当天的具体指标
So we just want to take that whole object and merge it on to the existing State,
我们想将整个对象合并到现有 state 上
which when this runs is just going to be an empty object.
当这个函数运行时 将为空的对象
And next, when add.entry matches what we want to do is,
接着 如果符合 ADD_ENTRY case
we want to say we want to return the exact same State but just as we did before,
则返回现有的 state 并且和之前一样
we want to go ahead and take action.entry which is the brand new entry
获取 action.entry entry 现在将是当天的崭新条目
for this specific day and just merge it onto the State.
并将其合并到 state 上
So really because we only have one Reducer here and that's all we're ever going to have,
我们只有这里的一个 Reducer 并且始终只有一个
the State is just going to be one big object as
state 将是一个很庞大的对象 并且始终是这样
it always is with each of the keys and that
该对象上的每个键
object representing a specific day and each of
都代表特定的某一天
those values representing the specific metrics for that day.
每个值代表当天的具体指标
So that's why in both Recieve Entries, as well as,
因此在 RECEIVE_ENTRIES 和 ADD_ENTRY case 中
Add Entry we can just take whatever on the specific action and just merge it
我们可以获取该特定 action 上的信息
into the State because our State is really just one big object for days.
并将其合并到 state 上 因为 state 是针对所有日期的庞大对象